Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Staff / Counselors files
  - Alphabetical 1925-1959
    - Selbert, Mrs. Norma (1936) (Box 27)
    - Selleck, Richard (1946) (Box 27)
    - Seymour, Paul (1930) (Box 27)
    - Shellington, Miss Dorothy (1948) (Box 27)
    - Sikorovsky, Eugene (1944) (Box 27)
    - Shields, Mr. Henderson (1926-1931) (Box 27)
    - Simrall, Mr. James "Duckey" (1929-1931) (Box 27)
    - Skeen, Mr. Samuel M. (1931) (Box 27)
    - Slabaugh, Dale (1948) (Box 27)
    - Slaughter, Mr. Edliff "Butch" (1925-1931) (Box 27)
    - Sleight, Mr. James D. (1930-1931) (Box 27)
    - Smith, Mr. Arthur (1930-1933) (Box 27)
    - Smith, Mr. Donald (1925) (Box 27)
    - Smith, Glenn (1948) (Box 27)
    - Smith, W. Dow (1936) (Box 27)
    - Snell, Judson (1938) (Box 27)
    - Soderstrom, Mr. Vic (1928-1930) (Box 27)
    - Spencer, James (1945) (Box 27)
    - Stitt, Mr. Clyde (1936) (Box 27)
    - Stocking, Mr. Bruce "Doc" (1928-1931) (Box 27)
    - Strang, Dr. James (1927) (Box 27)
    - Tefft, Mrs. William (1931) (Box 27)
    - Thiel, Mr. Arthur (1926) (Box 27)
    - Thomas, Dick (1945) (Box 27)
    - Thomas, Kendall P. (1946) (Box 27)
    - Thompson, Raymond (1945) (Box 27)
    - Throop, Harold (1946) (Box 27)
    - Tolfree, John (1948) (Box 27)
    - Traphagen, Mr. Clarence (1925-1927) (Box 27)
    - Unger, Mr. Paxton J. (1927) (Box 27)
    - Van Houten, Charles (1937) (Box 27)
    - Waldron, Mr. Lawrence (1947) (Box 27)
    - Walker, Ted (1942) (Box 27)
    - Wagner, Mr. John (1928) (Box 27)
    - Warner, Mr. Oscar F. (1926) (Box 27)
    - Warthin, Mr. Tom (1927-1928) (Box 27)
    - Wasaquam, Andrew (1941) (Box 27)
    - Watson, Mr. Tom (1926-1932) (Box 27)
    - Weeks, William (1936) (Box 27)
    - Weldon, Richard C. (1949) (Box 27)
    - Wellington, Fred (1941) (Box 27)
    - Wells, William D. (1934) (Box 27)
    - Westerman, Mr. Harold (1938) (Box 27)
    - Westfall, Bob (1940) (Box 27)
    - Wheeler, Lawrence (1935) (Box 27)
    - Whitaker, Wayne L. (1934) (Box 27)
    - Whitely, Mr. Jack (1932) (Box 27)
    - Williamson, Aubra C. (1945) (Box 27)
    - Willis, Kendall (1941) (Box 27)
    - Winchester, Dick (1946-1949) (Box 27)
    - Wingerden, Arthur (1945) (Box 27)
    - Witherspoon, Thomas Worden (1950) (Box 27)
    - Whittemore, Hal (1938) (Box 27)
    - Williams, Richard G. (1950) (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Eugene M. (1945) (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Howard D. (1947) (Box 27)
    - Wood, Mr. Frank A. (1927-1933) (Box 27)
    - Workman, Rollin W. (1950) (Box 27)
    - Wright, Bernard (1942) (Box 27)
    - Wuerfel, Ted (1933) (Box 27)
    - Wyatt, Mr. John B. (1928-1930) (Box 27)
    - Yamagiwa, Mr. Joseph (1931) (Box 27)
    - Yinger, Mr. Dempster (1928-1930) (Box 27)
    - Yinger, Milton (1936) (Box 27)
    - Yinger, Paul (1934) (Box 27)
    - Yacom, Dean (1938) (Box 27)
  - Chronological 1950-1967 (Box 27)
    - 1950
      - Ackman, Keith W. (Box 28)
      - Erbe, William E. (Box 28)
      - Harper, James F. (Box 28)
      - Heemstra, Raymond W. (Box 28)
      - Jackson, Virginia Bialy (Box 28)
      - Kretchmar, J. Lauran (Box 28)
      - Price, Evan Charles (Box 28)
      - Slaker, Richard P. (Box 28)
      - Underwood, Dave (Box 28)
    - 1951
      - Bonfiglio, Ralph G. (Box 28)
      - Cronin, Earl (Box 28)
      - Darling, John Allan (Box 28)
      - Gifford, Allan H. (Box 28)
      - Gifford, Bruce G. (Box 28)
      - Guemple, Charles E. (Box 28)
      - Healy, Donald W. (Box 28)
      - Heath, Robert G. (includes Elsye) (Box 28)
      - Marquette, Gene (Box 28)
      - McClelland, Robert L. (Box 28)
      - Server, Harvey W. (Box 28)
      - Staebler, Mike (Box 28)
      - Stuart, Douglas A. (Box 28)
      - Timmerman, Edward G. (Box 28)
      - True, Wesley O. (Box 28)
      - Vreeland, Bruce (Box 28)
    - 1952
      - Atkinson, Don I. (Box 28)
      - Beemer, Richard B. (Box 28)
      - Bennett, Lyle F. (Box 28)
      - Burns, Robert D. (Box 28)
      - Cragg, Graham S. (Box 28)
      - Felzer, Bert L. (Box 28)
      - Goetz, John Thomas (Box 28)
      - Graf, David L. (Box 28)
      - Guettler, Eugene G. (Box 28)
      - Gwinn, Paul Allan (Box 28)
      - Hayes, Edward B. (Box 28)
      - Lewis, Bob (Box 28)
      - Lord, William K. (Box 28)
      - Moore, Harry Clay (Box 28)
      - Moore, Noel Samuel (Box 28)
      - Riedesel, Wilson A. (Box 28)
      - Rogers, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (Box 28)
      - Schaefer, John David (Box 28)
      - Smith, Dave (includes Steve) (Box 28)
      - Smith, Richard Conrad (Box 28)
      - Stevens, Dale Clinton (Box 28)
      - Wade, Francis M. (Box 28)
      - Walker, Mary Jane (Box 28)
      - Webb, William Duncan (includes Nancy Helen) (Box 28)
      - Weber, Robert Walter (Box 28)
      - Wells, William P. (Box 28)
      - Wilson, Winston Bruce
      - Young, Jon Leon (Box 28)
    - 1953
      - Anderson, Roger A. (Box 28)
      - Barrett, William H. (Box 28)
      - Bateman, William T. (Box 28)
      - Brief, Douglas J. (Box 28)
      - Brown, Richard Seymour (Box 28)
      - Burns, Alden (Monte) B. (Box 28)
      - Chase, Christopher S. (Box 28)
      - Foster, Emerson Clair (Box 28)
      - Gilman, John L. (Box 28)
      - Goodell, David L. (Box 28)
      - Gossett, Tom (Box 28)
      - Hafemeister, Larry (Box 28)
      - Hubly, John A. (Box 28)
      - Nason, Agnes Jane (Box 28)
      - Price, Tom (Box 28)
      - Robles, Rudolph K. (Box 28)
      - Sacquety, Charles W. (Box 28)
      - Smith, Donald F. (Box 28)
      - VanHook, Jim H. (Box 28)
      - Wallgren, Ivan B. (Box 28)
      - Weber, Thomas W. (Box 28)
      - Wilson, Pat (Box 28)
    - 1954
      - Allinder, William F. (Box 29)
      - Bremer, Windham (Box 29)
      - Brown, James R. (Box 29)
      - Bunker, Thomas P., Jr. (Box 29)
      - Coddington, Donn (Box 29)
      - Cowart, Jack L. (Box 29)
      - Cramton, Kenneth G. (Box 29)
      - Elliott, Verda Lillian (Box 29)
      - Enck, Thomas E. (Box 29)
      - Kraus, Willis Keith (Box 29)
      - Lefler, Covert C. (Box 29)
      - Margowski, Johnny (Box 29)
      - Nilsen, Nick (Box 29)
      - O'Neill, Charles B. (Box 29)
      - Pade, Gordon James (Box 29)
      - Struever, Stuart (Box 29)
      - Wanty, Dean J. (Box 29)
      - Wood, David (Box 29)
    - 1955
      - Borusch, Roberts (Box 29)
      - Browne, Brian (Box 29)
      - Conibear, Robert J. (Box 29)
      - Guggisberg, Jamie (Box 29)
      - Jones, Sam (Box 29)
      - Mercke, William F. "Bill" (Box 29)
      - Morris, Mike (Box 29)
      - Richard, Walter (Box 29)
      - Steed, Mrs. Anne (Box 29)
      - Stewart, J. Robert (Box 29)
      - VanderSchalie, Arnold E. (Box 29)
      - Van Fleet, Corey (Box 29)
      - Wallingford, Robert O. (Box 29)
      - Wealch, J. Donald (Box 29)
      - Wear, Robert (includes Louise) (Box 29)
      - Weaver, Richard (Box 29)
      - Wiggins, Jack (Box 29)
      - Wilson, Terry (Box 29)
      - Wilson, Thomas (Box 29)
    - 1956
      - Baldwin, Dick (Box 29)
      - Barton, James (Box 29)
      - Breiholz, Dave (Box 29)
      - Coates, Jim (Box 29)
      - De Waard, Elliott John (Jack) (Box 29)
      - Dunham, Lance (Box 29)
      - Graham, Bill (Box 29)
      - Harrelson, Dave (Box 29)
      - Kress, Tom (Box 29)
      - Larned, Steve (includes Bill) (Box 29)
      - Lasch, Henry Albert (Box 29)
      - Milward, Brint (includes John Burton & Greg) (Box 29)
      - Newburn, Mike (Box 29)
      - Ratterman, Mike (Box 29)
      - Venema, William J. (Box 29)
    - 1957
      - Bogrette, David Wentworth (Box 30)
      - Bush, Paul Earl (Box 30)
      - Conklin, Frederic L., M.D. (Box 30)
      - Davy, Shirley (Box 30)
      - Detwyler, Thomas (Box 30)
      - Enck, Steve (Box 30)
      - Erwin, Jack (Box 30)
      - Farr, Frederick Towne, Jr. (Box 30)
      - Harrelson, Jim (Box 30)
      - Larned, Steve (Box 30)
      - Makowski, Joseph A. (Box 30)
      - Orcutt, William Burton "Bill" (Box 30)
      - Parke, Donald (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 30)
      - Schreur, David (Box 30)
      - Swadling, Jerry (Box 30)
      - Walsh, Terry Rodney (Box 30)
      - Wuerfel, Frederick P. (Box 30)
      - Zill, Ronald Stephen (Box 30)
    - 1958
      - Arndt, Paul Lambur "Bud" (Box 30)
      - Beach, Gurney D. (Box 30)
      - Burleigh, Charles L. "Chuck" (Box 30)
      - Coulter, Leland Everett Jr. "Pete" (Box 30)
      - Fairbank, Jonathan Thomas "Jon" (Box 30)
      - Fox, James E. "Jim" (Box 30)
      - Jedwill, Fred Warren "Fritz" (Box 30)
      - Meacham, John Palmer (Box 30)
      - McDermott, Dan (Box 30)
      - Miller, Thomas William "Tom" (Box 30)
      - Olson, Raymond S. (Box 30)
      - Powers, Robert Warren "Bob" (Box 30)
      - Richardson, James MacGregor "Mac" (Box 30)
      - Valek, Philip Bryce "Phil" (Box 30)
    - 1959
      - Baldwin, Timothy "Tim" (Box 30)
      - Fenstermacher, Joseph "Joe" (Box 30)
      - Firlik, Robert S. "Bob" (Box 30)
      - Grady, Michael (Box 30)
      - Hillock, Robert Richard (Box 30)
      - Lyke, Murray G. (Box 30)
      - Mayer, George John (Box 30)
      - McCormick, James Hume (Box 30)
      - Miller, George William (Box 30)
      - Murphy, M. Wilson (Box 30)
      - Reed, Michael E. "Mike" (Box 30)
      - Sheasby, John Frederick (Box 30)
      - Shermeta, Dennis (Box 30)
      - Smith, Richard F. "Dick" (Box 30)
      - Weathers, Thomas "Tom" (Box 30)
      - Wilcox, Robert Stimson (Box 30)
    - 1960
      - Ashrafi, Bahman (Box 30)
      - Beuhler, Robert James (Box 30)
      - Cordes, Kurt Lee (Box 30)
      - Dobkin, William Edward (Box 30)
      - Everhardus, John Arthur (Box 30)
      - Fortney, James Milton (Box 30)
      - Geahan, Richard Hale (Box 30)
      - Glass, William Finis, Jr. (Box 30)
      - Goerke, Donald L. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 30)
      - Hartsook, David Michael (Box 30)
      - Hodge, Charles Edwin (Box 30)
      - Keating, John Raymond (Box 30)
      - Morison, John A. (Box 30)
      - Nelson, John Allen (Box 30)
      - Peters, David Owen (Box 30)
      - Sluyter, Raymond Edwin (Box 30)
      - Smith, James Douglas (Box 30)
      - Sullivan, Mary Patricia (Box 30)
      - Warner, Jim Bert (Box 30)
      - Weimer, Peter Miller (Box 30)
      - Zbinden, David William (Box 30)
    - 1961
      - Ackerman, Jon Arno (Box 30)
      - Coin, Larry Lavern (Box 30)
      - Colby, William "Bill" (Box 30)
      - Dobson, Russell T. (Box 30)
      - Evans, Kenneth R. (Box 30)
      - Gordon, Robert D. (Box 30)
      - Hodges, Don (Box 30)
      - Hummel, Jerome A. (Box 30)
      - Hush, Lawrence W. (Box 30)
      - Jacobsen, Barry (Box 30)
      - Kriemer, James Dunlap "Jay" (Box 30)
      - Marx, Charles Hardy (Box 30)
      - Maxwell, John W. (Box 30)
      - Wernette, John D. Courcy (Box 30)
    - 1962
      - Albrecht, John (Box 31)
      - Allen, John (Box 31)
      - Berger, Barron D. Jr. "Buzz" (Box 31)
      - Boyer, Thomas Henry (Box 31)
      - Brockman, William George (Box 31)
      - Denise, Jerome Robert "Jerry" (Box 31)
      - Doerr, Richard Samuel (Box 31)
      - Duell, William P. "Bill" (Box 31)
      - Greene, Steven Hardy (Box 31)
      - Haughey, James W. (Box 31)
      - Johnston, Richard Ronald (Box 31)
      - Kinney, Paul E. (Box 31)
      - Klores, Stanley Whitehouse (Box 31)
      - Mewborn, William M. "Doc" (Box 31)
      - Miller, Jr., Robert (Box 31)
      - Munson, Charles T. (Box 31)
      - Nardizzi, Pasquale (Box 31)
      - Nelson, Gregory Karl (Box 31)
      - Readmond, Frances (Box 31)
      - Shambaugh, Gregory Randall "Greg" (Box 31)
      - Viger, David N., Jr. (Box 31)
      - Whitehouse, William (Box 31)
    - 1963
      - Andrews, Paul E. (Box 31)
      - Baker, Robert S. "Bob" (Box 31)
      - Capps, Kenneth Larry "Larry" (Box 31)
      - Clement, Robert Leroy, Jr. "Bob" (Box 31)
      - Creps, Harry James (Box 31)
      - Daley, Leonard Henry (Box 31)
      - Hale, Norman (Box 31)
      - Idema, John Blaine (Box 31)
      - Klein, Gregory Peter (Box 31)
      - Kuehn, William Neal (Box 31)
      - La Bay, Michael J. (Box 31)
      - Liles, John H. (Box 31)
      - McDowell, James William (Box 31)
      - Morse, Peter Harwood (Box 31)
      - Nylund, John A. (Box 31)
    - 1964
      - Bade, James A. "Jim" (Box 31)
      - Beierwaltes, Andrew G. "Andy" (Box 31)
      - Bruggeman, Anthony P. "Tony" (Box 31)
      - Collins, James H. "Jim" (Box 31)
      - Green, Peter Douglas (Box 31)
      - Jankowski, Martin Lee (Box 31)
      - Jones, John R. (Box 31)
      - Krauskopf, John S. (Box 31)
      - McDonald, Dennis (Box 31)
      - Mewborn, Jed Webster "Jed" (Box 31)
      - Murray, William W. "Bill" (Box 31)
      - Retter, Carl R. (Box 31)
      - Rhea, Thomas A. "Tom" (Box 31)
      - Streiff, Karl Daniel "Dan" (Box 31)
      - Van Zon, David D. (Box 31)
      - Walker, Lyle Adams (Box 31)
      - Weber, Lois Jean (Box 31)
      - Whitehouse, Jim Keith (Box 31)
      - Willeke, Robert N. "Bob" (Box 31)
    - 1965
      - Clayton, Thomas S. "Thom" (Box 31)
      - Grady, Steven (Box 31)
      - Graham, John (Box 31)
      - Jones, Jerry C. (Box 31)
      - Kollar, James A. (Box 31)
      - Kollar, John (Box 31)
      - Kriesch, Ronald (Box 31)
      - Ledebuhr, Robert Larry (Box 31)
      - Lonskey, John (Box 31)
      - McDonald, Timothy Joseph (Box 31)
      - Woodruff, Michael Lester (Box 31)
    - 1966
      - Ackerly, Rex C. (Box 31)
      - Bade, Gordon Lawrence "Gordy" (Box 31)
      - Bartlett, Dennis A. (Box 31)
      - Brown, Gary Edward (Box 31)
      - Brunelle, Francis Joseph "Frank" (Box 31)
      - Day, Robert Edwin "Bob" (Box 31)
      - DeFiore, Robert Brian "Brian" (Box 31)
      - Foley, Fred Allen (Box 31)
      - Godwin, Luther P. (Box 31)
      - LaForte, Martin E. "Marty" (Box 31)
      - Leighty, James C. (Box 31)
      - Marshall, Peter Charles (Box 31)
      - Narins, Joseph Paul "Joe" (Box 31)
      - Peters, Richard "Rick" (Box 31)
      - Sandy, Robert "Bob" (Box 31)
      - Schrubkowski, Walentin "Wally" (Box 31)
      - Smith, Rosalie Scott (Box 31)
      - Sperry, Wayne Sheldon "Shelly" (Box 31)
      - Wildeboer, Marcis Kay (Box 31)
      - Wolf, Steven (Box 31)
    - 1967
      - Bauchman, John B. (Box 31)
      - Bryce, Gordon T. (Box 31)
      - Durastanti, Frank (Box 31)
      - Hanke, Kathleen (Box 31)
      - Kell, Gary W. (Box 31)
      - Kollar, James (Box 31)
      - Kollar, John (Box 31)
      - Long, Christopher F. (Box 31)
      - Long, Jon M. (Box 31)
      - Shotwell, James W. (Box 31)
      - Volz, Ken (Box 31)
      - Wilkins, L'Anse (Box 31)
      - Zachrich, Barton M. "Bart" (Box 31)
      - Zink, Jon (Box 31)
    - Staff Miscellaneous
      - Barclay, Charles (1942) (Box 31)
      - Besett, Ferne (1967) (Box 31)
      - Schumm, Albert (1946) (Box 31)
      - Tucker, Randy (1947-1949) (Box 31)
- Administrative and personal
  - Alaska trip 1934, 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous 1950s-1960s forms, etc. (Box 32)
  - 1959
    - Activity Reports (Box 32)
    - Daily health report sheets (Box 32)
    - Form letters (Box 32)
    - Mississaugas camper reports (Box 32)
    - Program (Box 32)
    - Rosters (Box 32)
    - Tribal reports (Box 32)
    - Tutoring (Box 32)
    - Waterfront personnel and rules (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - 1960
    - Activity Reports (Box 32)
    - Campers (Box 32)
    - Camper reports sheets (Box 32)
      (one cabin retained as sample)
    - Form letters (Box 32)
    - Forms (Box 32)
    - General staff instructions (Box 32)
    - Inventories (Box 32)
    - Program file (Box 32)
    - Reunion file (Box 32)
    - Rosters (Box 32)
    - Staff miscellaneous (Box 32)
    - Tribal reports (Box 32)
  - 1961
    - Campers (Box 32)
    - Camper reports sheets (Box 32)
    - Daily health report sheets (Box 32)
    - Form letters (Box 32)
    - Forms (Box 32)
    - Reunion file (Box 32)
    - Rosters (Box 32)
    - Trip reports (Box 32)
  - 1962-1966
    - American Camping Association 1966 (Box 32)
    - Campers 1966 (Box 32)
    - Enrollment by area 1963 (Box 32)
    - Form letters 1964 (Box 32)
    - Program file 1963 (Box 32)
    - Religious preference 1962 (Box 32)
    - Religious preference 1963 (Box 32)
  - Counselor contracts
    - 1958 (Box 32)
    - 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - 1963-1967, 4 folders (Box 32)
  - Herbert Twining personal 1961-1966, 3 folders (Box 32)
    (some gaps)